Adult Education Association (AEA-USA)/American Association for Adult and Continuing Education (AAACE) Records
Adult Education Association (AEA-USA)/American Association for Adult and Continuing Education (AAACE) Records
- [Part III] Historical files
  - AEA
    - Adult Leadership, 1952-1957; 1960-1961,; 1975-1977,; 1978-1979; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - Lifelong Learninq, 1973-1979 (Box 56)
    - Adult Education Materials, 1952-1965; undated; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - NEA Conference, 1981 (Box 56)
    - AEA/NAPSAE Plan of Consolidation Adult Education Materials, 1979-1981 (Box 56)
    - Sears Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
    - Sears Final Report, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
    - AEA Directory, 1965 (Box 56)
    - Old Annual Reports, 1952-1981 (Box 56)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 56)
    - Annual Report, 1979 (Box 56)
    - Steering Committee Meeting, St. Louis, Missouri, 1980 (Box 56)
    - Proposal [for] Development and Funding AEA/USA Adult and Continuing Education Learning Center, 1978 (Box 56)
    - AEA Endowment Fund, 1960-1962; 1982 (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Recruitment Letter, 1965-1967; undated
    - AEA Research Proposal, 1970; history (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Joint Membership, 1965 (Box 56)
    - AEA Union, 1975; history (Box 56)
    - Adult Basic Education Study, AEA History, 1965-1966 (Box 56)
    - AEA History: AEA Clearinghouse on Adult Education in Latin America (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Conference of Adult Education Association, 1964 (Box 56)
    - Conference of Adult Education Associations: Model of Information Retrieval System, 1964 (Box 56)
    - AEA Constitution, 1977 (Box 56)
    - AEA Building Fund, 1978 (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Legislation, 1966 (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Annual Report, 1955 (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Organizational Services Contract with U.S. Office of Education, 1965 (Box 56)
    - AEA History: Proposal to National Endowment for the Arts, 1970; 1973 (Box 56)
- [Part III] Office files
  - AAACE 1983-1987
    - Annual Reports, Apr 1983 (Box 57)
    - Board of Directors, 1982: Nov (Box 57)
    - Board of Directors, 1984: Feb, Apr, Nov; 3 folders (Box 57)
    - Board of Directors, 1985: Nov; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Board of Directors, 1987: Apr, Oct; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Executive Committee, 1983: Feb, Nov/Dec; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Executive Committee, 1984: Feb, Apr, Jul, Nov; 5 folders (Box 57)
    - Executive Committee, 1985: Aug (Box 57)
    - Executive Committee, 1986: Feb, Apr, Jul, Oct; 7 folders (Box 57)
    - Executive Committee, 1987: Feb, Jul; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Conferences, 1983: Apr, Nov; includes Executive Director's Notebook; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Conferences, 1987: Oct; program (Box 58)
    - Division reports, Oct. 1987 (Box 58)
  - AEA 1958-1982
    - Legislative Report, 1961-1964; 9 folders (Box 58)
    - Facts and Fiqures, 1963; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Public Information Project (Box 58)
    - Publications Readership Survey (Box 58)
    - Education About Education, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Selected references on adult education, Division of Adult Education (Box 58)
    - NAEC News, 1968; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - NAEC Clearinghouse brochures (Box 58)
    - Legislative summary, 1961 (Box 58)
    - Holiday message, 1958 (Box 58)
    - Christmas dreetings, 1963 (Box 58)
    - Literacy packet, 1962 (Box 58)
    - NAPSAE-AEA European tour, 1965 (Box 58)
    - NAPSAE European Tour brochures (Box 58)
    - Pipe Lines letters (Box 58)
    - Automotive Safety Foundation Questionnaire, Adult Writing Classes (Box 58)
    - Adult Elementary Education, Research Project (Wanda M. Wilcox), 1963 (Box 58)
    - Guidance Services Survey (Mrs. Bernice Hamberg), 1964 (Box 58)
    - State associations (Box 58)
    - Letters to congressmen and senators (Box 58)
    - Adult Basic Education Act, 1962 (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous mailings (Box 58)
    - NAPSAE posters, 1959-1963; undated; 6 folders (Box 58)
    - NAPSAE promotion packet, 1961; undated; 4 folders (Box 58)
    - Idea file, 1959-1964; 43 folders (Box 59)
    - Public School Adult Education, 1957-1960; 16 folders (Box 59)
    - Aids, 1954-1955; 4 folders (Box 59)
    - Helps, 1953-1955; 5 folders (Box 59)
    - Aids, helps, 1955-1957; 10 folders (Box 59)
    - Napsack, President's Newsletter (Box 59)
    - News sheet, 1958-1960; 11 folders (Box 59)
    - News From NAPSAE, 1958 (Box 59)
    - Legislative Flash!, 1966-1967 (Box 59)
    - Legislative Report, 1967 (Box 59)
    - Adult Education Legislation (Box 59)
- [Part III] Publications
  - AAACE monographs
    - Membership directories, 1984-1988 (Box 59)
    - AAACE Adult Education Series, 1988; 4 items (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous monographs, 1983-1991; 11 items (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous monographs, 1983-1991; 2 items (Box 60)
  - AAACE periodicals
    - AAACE Newsletter, 1983-1987 (Box 60)
    - Adult Basic Education, 1991 (Box 60)
    - Adult Education, 1961-1967; 1981-1983 (Box 60)
    - Adult Education Quarterly, 1983-1991 (Box 60)
    - Adult Learning (supersedes Lifelong Learning), 1989-1991 (Box 60)
    - Adult Literacy & Basic Education, 1979; 1989 (Box 60)
    - Lifelong Learning (superseded by Adult Learning), 1977-1989 (Box 60)
    - Online, 1987-1992 (Box 61)
  - AEA monographs
    - AEA Professional Development Series, 1981; 3 items (Box 61)
    - AEA Handbook Series in Adult Education, 1980-1981; 10 items (Box 61)
    - Leadership Pamphlets, undated (Box 61)
    - Adult Education: Theory and Method, 1962; 1965,; undated; 4 items (Box 61)
    - Current Information Series, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 62)
    - Membership Directory, 1981 (Box 62)
    - Annual Reports, 1979; 1980 (Box 62)
    - Miscellaneous monographs, 1956-1985; undated; 18 items (Box 62)
  - AEA periodicals
    - Adult Education Dissertation Abstracts, 1935-1962; 1963-1967 (Box 62)
    - The Leader's Digest, 1953-1955 (Box 62)
  - NAPSAE monographs
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1981; undated (Box 62)
  - NAPSAE periodicals
    - Administrators Swap Shop, 1973-1974 (Box 62)
    - NAPSAE Exchange, 1981 (Box 62)
    - Techniques, 1973-1981 (Box 62)